Well, there are countless libraries that
we could cover and I don't have time to
cover all of them, but I am going to
show you how you could find out more
about them yourself. So, for example, um
one of the libraries you might want to
use is something called low dash. Do you
remember when I made you use a reducer
or use reduce to go over an array to
find the maximum number? Well, it turns
out if you use the low dash library, you
could have put underscore.max
and boom,
it would give you the maximum number.
And it just has a whole bunch of
pre-built functions that could have made
your life a whole lot easier if we had
used libraries earlier. So, that's
pretty cool. Uh maybe you like building
charts. Um well, there's this library
called chartjs and it can let you build
charts like this. And it's pretty cool.
Um, and they've got pretty good
documentation about how to do that. Um,
so what you can do is you can come to
cdnjs.com
and click on libraries and then you can
scroll through and see so many libraries
that are available for you to use. Um,
so like for example this pdf.js
um it says there are zero known
vulnerabilities. Um,
and this will allow you to um this will
allow you to read PDFs using JavaScript.
Um, scrolling down some more. Let's see
if we can find another one. Um,
there are just so many things that you
can do with JavaScript, so many
libraries out there that will make your
life easier. And so I encourage you to
go take a look at those and see if there
isn't some code out there that will make
your life so much easier.